<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>High voltage components on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
    <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/categories/high-voltage-components/</link>
    <description>Recent content in High voltage components on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</description>
    <image>
      <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
      <url>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</url>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:46:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.senkuogroup.com/categories/high-voltage-components/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ZW43-12F-High-Voltage-Intelligent-Vacuum-Circuit-Breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw43-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker-zw43-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw43-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker-zw43-12/</guid>
      <description>ZW43-12 series outdoor high-voltage AC intelligent vacuum circuit breaker (hereinafter referred to as is an outdoor power distribution switchgear with a rated voltage of 12kV and three-phase AC 50Hz. It is mainly composed of the ZW43-12 outdoor high-voltage AC vacuum circuit breaker body , DK series distribution automation feeder terminals, external voltage transformers and control cables, etc., and can be equipped with lightning arresters, single-side isolating switches or double-side isolating switches according to user needs. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-40.5-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-40.5-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-40.5-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32-40.5 outdoor high-voltage vacuum circuit breaker adopts mature box-type sealing structure. It has good sealing performance, so that it is not affected by the external environment, and it is a maintenance-free product. Its spring operating mechanism adopts direct-action chain main drive and multi-stage tripping system, which has high operation reliability and is a good product for pole-mounted circuit breakers. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-24-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-24-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-24-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32-24/630-25 outdoor high-voltage AC vacuum circuit breaker is an outdoor power distribution equipment with a rated voltage of 24kV and three-phase AC 50Hz. It is a switchgear developed by our company according to the long-term planning of my country&amp;#39;s power system and relevant standards. It has the ability to break and close the load current, overload current and short-circuit current in the line. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-12G-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-12g-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:16:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-12g-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32-12(G)/T series outdoor high-voltage AC intelligent vacuum circuit breaker is an outdoor high-voltage power distribution switchgear with a rated voltage of 12kV and three-phase AC 50Hz, mainly used for breaking, It can close the load current, overload current and short-circuit current in the power system. It is suitable for protection and control in the power distribution system of substations and industrial and mining enterprises, and can also be used in places that require frequent operations such as rural power grids. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-12F-High-Voltage-Intelligent-Vacuum-Circuit-Breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 12:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32F-12F outdoor high-voltage AC intelligent vacuum circuit breaker is a user boundary switch independently developed by our company. It is mainly composed of ZW32-12 type outdoor vacuum circuit breaker body, FDR fault detection controller and external voltage transformer. The three parts are electrically connected through aviation sockets and outdoor sealed control cables. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW20A-12-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20a-12-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 12:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20a-12-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW20A-12 outdoor high-voltage AC vacuum circuit breaker (hereinafter referred to as circuit breaker) is an outdoor power distribution equipment with a rated voltage of 12kV and three-phase AC 50Hz. It uses vacuum arc extinguishing and SF6 gas as the insulating medium, and is an improved product of ZW20-12 column-mounted vacuum circuit breaker. The box body adopts the gas sealing, explosion-proof and insulating structure technology imported from Japan Toshiba Company VSP5, and the sealing performance of the inlet and outlet conduits has also been improved.  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW20-12F-smart-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20-12f-smart-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 11:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20-12f-smart-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW20-12F intelligent vacuum circuit breaker is an advanced product improved from ZW20-12 pole-mounted circuit breaker and FZW28F-12 outdoor boundary vacuum load switch. It has manual and electric operation functions. The switch body adopts Japan Toshiba&amp;#39;s VSP5-12 maintenance-free load switch, and the mature cold-rolled steel box-type sealing structure has good sealing performance, so that it is not affected by the external environment and is a maintenance-free product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FZW28-12F-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/fzw28-12f-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/fzw28-12f-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</guid>
      <description>FZW28(A)-12F outdoor boundary vacuum load switch (VSP5-12 switch body and FDR-01 controller) has fault detection function, protection control function and communication function. It is installed on 10KV overhead line and can realize automatic cutting of single phase Ground faults and phase-to-phase short-circuit faults are automatically isolated. The installation point is suitable for the responsibility demarcation point of the user&amp;#39;s incoming line of 10KV distribution line, and it can also be applied for the branch line connection that meets the requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AB-3S-12-permanent-magnet-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ab-3s-12-permanent-magnet-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ab-3s-12-permanent-magnet-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>AB-3S-12 series outdoor high-voltage vacuum permanent magnet circuit breaker is a new generation of column-mounted vacuum circuit breaker newly developed by integrating advanced technology at home and abroad, adopting new design concepts, and using high-tech means. This product can be used as a switch on the 10kV side of the main transformer of a 35kV substation and a 10kV outgoing line switch, and can also be used as a pole-mounted switch in a distribution network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSP5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/vsp5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/vsp5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</guid>
      <description>VSP5-12 series outdoor vacuum boundary switch is a combination circuit breaker with isolation, rated voltage 12KV, three-phase AC 50HZ high-voltage outdoor switchgear, the built-in voltage 12KV is converted to 220V operating voltage, mainly used for switching on and off rural power grids and urban power grids And load current, overload current, short circuit current of small power system. The overall structure of the product is a three-phase common box type. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
