<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Low voltage switchgear on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd.</title>
    <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/low-voltage-switchgear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Low voltage switchgear on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd.</description>
    <image>
      <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd.</title>
      <url>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/8.png</url>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/8.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 15:26:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/low-voltage-switchgear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GZDW-Intelligent-High-Frequency-DC-Control-Panel</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/pk-series-microcomputer-protection-measurement-and-control-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 15:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/pk-series-microcomputer-protection-measurement-and-control-screen/</guid>
      <description>PK series microcomputer protection measurement and control panels are used in substation distribution substations with voltage levels of 35KV and below. Provide intelligent and networked measurement, protection and control functions for each high-voltage equipment in the station, and at the same time communicate with the upper master station in real time to realize the comprehensive automation of the substation distribution station. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/gcs-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 12:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/gcs-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>GCS series combined low-voltage switchgear (hereinafter referred to as GCS complete switchgear). It is suitable for the power system of AC 50~60HZ, rated working voltage AC 380V, rated insulation voltage 660V, 1600KVA and below distribution transformer as power distribution, power, lighting, reactive power compensation, motor control center, and designed in the standard cabinet The mixed system of fixed scheme and withdrawal scheme can meet the different needs of users. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MNS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 11:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>MNS is a modular and multi-functional low-voltage power distribution cabinet, which is used in all low-voltage systems that require high reliability in the fields of metallurgy, petroleum, chemical industry, industrial and mining enterprises, and infrastructure: power distribution box motor control system. The counter structure adopted by MNS has high flexibility. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
