<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
    <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</description>
    <image>
      <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
      <url>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</url>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 11:50:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.senkuogroup.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JP-series-integrated-distribution-box-compensation-control-terminal-lighting</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/jp-series-integrated-distribution-box-compensation-control-terminal-lighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 11:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/jp-series-integrated-distribution-box-compensation-control-terminal-lighting/</guid>
      <description>JP series outdoor comprehensive distribution box is designed to meet the requirements of standardization, miniaturization and outdoor type of rural low-voltage power distribution equipment. It integrates power distribution, metering, protection, overload, short circuit, phase loss, undervoltage, Current over-current protection, zero line disconnection protection on the power supply side, automatic reclosing and opening, lightning protection, and capacitor reactive power compensation are integrated, providing a guarantee for safe electricity use in rural areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LKF-transformer-protection-switch-box</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/lkf-transformer-protection-switch-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 10:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/lkf-transformer-protection-switch-box/</guid>
      <description>The transformer protection switch box uses intelligent components to detect the operating current, which can accurately judge the relevant electrical operating conditions. In the event of: overload, short circuit, overvoltage, current imbalance, phase failure, leakage, etc., the smart device can trip within 0.2 seconds according to the above conditions, and automatically reclose the switch about 10 seconds after tripping. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PZ30-modularized-terminal-combined-electric-appliance</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/pz30-modularized-terminal-combined-electric-appliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 10:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/pz30-modularized-terminal-combined-electric-appliance/</guid>
      <description>Pz30 modularized terminal combination electric appliance is a new type of product developed in our country in recent years. It is widely used in industrial and mining enterprises, shops, hospitals, stations, ports, high-rise buildings and residential buildings, etc., as a complete set of equipment for circuit power distribution and control, and protects the circuit from overload, short-circuit leakage, and overvoltage Combined electrical appliances It is used in the end circuit of single-phase three-wire or three-phase five-wire with AC frequency 50Hz, rated voltage 220V or 380V, and maximum total load current of 100A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JXF-series-wall-mounted-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/jxf-series-wall-mounted-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/jxf-series-wall-mounted-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>JXF indoor wall-mounted control box, all products are bent and welded by unbending steel plates, and the surface is electrostatically sprayed with epoxy resin, which is beautiful and durable. The box is equipped with an installation base plate, which can be installed with electrical equipment, and the door can be opened more than 90 degrees and rotated flexibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFW-12-series-cable-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/dfw-12-series-cable-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/dfw-12-series-cable-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>DFW-12 outdoor high-voltage cable distribution box is specially used at the cable node of AC 12kV cable system to distribute electric energy. Its connection method is simple and convenient, and has the characteristics of full insulation, full sealing, corrosion resistance, maintenance-free, and exposed safety parts. It solves the problems of cable T connection and ring network power supply with multiple incoming and outgoing lines with advanced technology. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFW-12-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station-cable-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/dfw-12-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station-cable-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/dfw-12-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station-cable-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>DFW series European-style high-voltage cable branch box is widely used in the node connection of 10KV cable system, and is the main electrical equipment for collecting and branching cables after they come out of the switch cabinet. DFW branch box is designed for outdoor maintenance-free operation, safe and reliable, its protection level is IP33~IP66, and the underground tap can withstand flooding. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LK-DFX-301-10-low-voltage-branch-box</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/lk-dfx-301-10-low-voltage-branch-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/lk-dfx-301-10-low-voltage-branch-box/</guid>
      <description>The branch box is divided into two categories according to its electrical composition: one type does not contain any switchgear, and there are only accessories for processing and connecting cable ends in the box. The structure is relatively simple, the volume is small, and the function is relatively</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stainless-steel-series-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/stainless-steel-series-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/stainless-steel-series-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>The stainless steel series distribution box is a kind of distribution box designed and assembled into various control functions according to the model and specification of the components. Since the size of the box body can be selected arbitrarily, the structure is compact to a quite perfect combination. Wall-mounted installation, it can be used as a see-through window and door, and the door panel is pasted with a sealing rubber strip to prevent rainwater from infiltrating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XJM-metering-box-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xjm-metering-box-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xjm-metering-box-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>XJM series metering boxes are suspended or embedded, suitable for the metering of one or more users in civil and commercial residences. The meter box has a multi-door structure, the main switch is installed in the left door, and the watt-hour meter is installed in the right door. , easy to operate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFW-40.5-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/dfw-40.5-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/dfw-40.5-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station/</guid>
      <description>ZGS-12 intelligent integrated substation American box substation is also called prefabricated substation or prefabricated substation. It is a kind of high-voltage switchgear, distribution transformer and low-voltage power distribution device. It is a factory prefabricated indoor and outdoor compact power distribution equipment arranged according to a certain wiring scheme, which is to organically combine functions such as transformer step-down and low-voltage power distribution. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YB33-wind-power-box-type-substation</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/yb33-wind-power-box-type-substation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/yb33-wind-power-box-type-substation/</guid>
      <description>ZGS-12 intelligent integrated substation American box substation is also called prefabricated substation or prefabricated substation. It is a kind of high-voltage switchgear, distribution transformer and low-voltage power distribution device. It is a factory prefabricated indoor and outdoor compact power distribution equipment arranged according to a certain wiring scheme, which is to organically combine functions such as transformer step-down and low-voltage power distribution. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZBW-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-European-style</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zbw-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-european-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zbw-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-european-style/</guid>
      <description>Resin insulated dry-type transformers are our company&amp;#39;s introduction of foreign advanced technology, and independently developed SCB10 and SCB11 series thin-insulated dry-type transformers with fillers. Because the coils are encapsulated by epoxy resin, they are flame retardant, fireproof, explosion-proof, maintenance-free, and pollution-free. , Small size, can be directly installed in the load center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZGS-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-American-style</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zgs-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-american-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zgs-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-american-style/</guid>
      <description>ZGS-12 intelligent integrated substation American box substation is also called prefabricated substation or prefabricated substation. It is a kind of high-voltage switchgear, distribution transformer and low-voltage power distribution device. It is a factory prefabricated indoor and outdoor compact power distribution equipment arranged according to a certain wiring scheme, which is to organically combine functions such as transformer step-down and low-voltage power distribution. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S11-M-10kV-oil-immersed-transformer</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/s11-m-10kv-oil-immersed-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/s11-m-10kv-oil-immersed-transformer/</guid>
      <description>S11-M series fully sealed oil-immersed power transformer has the advantages of low loss, low noise and high efficiency, which can achieve good energy saving effect and reduce pollution. Compared with the ordinary oil-immersed transformer, the fully-sealed transformer cancels the oil storage tank, and the change of oil volume is automatically adjusted and compensated by the elasticity of the corrugated sheet of the corrugated oil tank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S9-M-10kV-three-phase-oil-immersed-fully-sealed-power-transformer</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/s9-m-10kv-three-phase-oil-immersed-fully-sealed-power-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/s9-m-10kv-three-phase-oil-immersed-fully-sealed-power-transformer/</guid>
      <description>S9-M-10kV three-phase oil-immersed fully sealed power transformer is different from ordinary oil-immersed transformers. It cancels the oil storage tank, and the corrugated plate heat sink of the oil tank body is used for heat dissipation and cooling. Its elastic expansion and contraction compensates for the volume of the oil. increase or decrease.  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCB10-10kV-resin-insulated-dry-type-transformer</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/scb10-10kv-resin-insulated-dry-type-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/scb10-10kv-resin-insulated-dry-type-transformer/</guid>
      <description>Resin insulated dry-type transformers are our company&amp;#39;s introduction of foreign advanced technology, and independently developed SCB10 and SCB11 series thin-insulated dry-type transformers with fillers. Because the coils are encapsulated by epoxy resin, they are flame retardant, fireproof, explosion-proof, maintenance-free, and pollution-free. , Small size, can be directly installed in the load center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TBB-10-High-Voltage-Collective-Compensation-Device</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-collective-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-collective-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>The TBB-10 high-voltage collective compensation device mainly avoids the disadvantages of large local compensation investment, equipment maintenance, and decentralized operation management. The centralized compensation device is mainly used in 3-10kV three-phase power frequency AC power system with small load changes. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TBB-10-High-Voltage-Reactive-Power-Automatic-Compensation-Device</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>TBB-10 high-voltage reactive power automatic compensation device is suitable for reactive power automatic tracking compensation of 35kV, 10kV (6kV) buses in 220kV, 110kV, 35kV substations, and is mainly used in 3-35kV three-phase power frequency AC power systems with large load fluctuations , the use of centralized compensation still cannot meet the system requirements, often resulting in over-compensation or under-compensation. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LKGK-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>LCGK-12 fully insulated and fully enclosed inflatable metal switchgear referred to as inflatable cabinet is also known as common box type inflatable cabinet, sf6 inflatable cabinet. All its live parts are completely sealed in a 3.0mm thick stainless steel SF6 gas box, multiple branch switches can be installed in one gas box, so that the switchgear is not affected by the environment. It truly realizes functions such as maintenance-free, reliable operation, and unattended operation. The inflatable cabinet unit adopts a modular design, which can be flexibly expanded and scientifically combined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HXGN17-12-unit-AC-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn17-12-unit-ac-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn17-12-unit-ac-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>In the power supply system, it is used to break the load current and close the short-circuit current. The ring network cabinet is equipped with a vacuum load switch, and the replacement mechanism is a spring operating mechanism, which can be operated manually or electrically. The switch and isolating knife are equipped with a dry-action operating mechanism.  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HXGN15-12-box-type-fixed-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:18:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>The principle of ring network power supply: ring network power supply is generally composed of three basic units. The incoming and outgoing line cabinets are used as the ring network unit. When any line fails, it can be isolated in time, and the other unit maintains the continuous power supply of the certified user transformer branch. The user circuit ring network cabinet plays a role of protection and isolation for the transformer, which is convenient for maintenance and repair. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGN68-12-indoor-AC-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn68-12-indoor-ac-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:18:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn68-12-indoor-ac-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>The switchgear is a 3.6, 7.2, 12KV three-phase AC 50Hz single-bus section indoor complete device for receiving and distributing electric energy. It also has the functions of controlling, protecting and monitoring circuits, and can be used in various types of power plants, substations, industrial and mining enterprises, high-rise buildings, etc., and can also be combined with ring main units in switching stations. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYN28-12-armored-removable-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn28-12-armored-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:06:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn28-12-armored-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>KYN28-12 type GZS1armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear) is a three-phase AC 50Hz indoor complete power distribution device, used to receive and non-distribute 3-12KV network power and The circuit implements control protection and supervision. Various types of microcomputer integrated relay protection devices are installed on the panel of the relay chamber of this product, and can realize the intelligent control of the system. It has the functions of remote control, telemetry, remote signaling and remote adjustment, and is controlled by CAN bus with communication interface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGN66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:06:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>XGN66-12Z box-type fixed AC metal-enclosed switchgear referred to as switchgear, this product is suitable for power single busbars with a rated voltage of 3.6-12kv, three-phase AC 50hz, and a rated current of 630A-3150A. Double busbar and single busbar with bypass system are used for receiving and distributing electric energy. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYN28A-24-type-removable-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn28a-24-type-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn28a-24-type-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>This product is suitable for three-phase AC 50/60Hz power system, used to receive and distribute electric energy, and to control, protect and detect the circuit. The switchgear has two structural forms: armored cabinet and double busbar cabinet. It can be equipped with SF6 circuit breaker, VD4-24 circuit breaker, ZN72-24 fully insulated vacuum circuit breaker, and the secondary circuit is equipped with advanced and reliable control protection unit. The interior of the product adopts APG epoxy casting and reliable solid fully insulated busbar technology for full insulation design. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGN15-24-AC-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn15-24-ac-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn15-24-ac-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>XGN15-24 AC high-voltage sulfur hexafluoride ring network switchgear (hereinafter referred to as ring network cabinet) is a new generation of high-voltage electrical products successfully researched by our company by introducing foreign advanced technology and in accordance with the requirements of domestic home appliances and urban network transformation. Strict form test and long-term trial operation assessment, all technical performance indicators have reached the national inspection standards. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HXGN17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>HXGN17-40.5 high-voltage vacuum ring network switchgear hereinafter referred to as ring network cabinet is a 50Hz AC three-phase indoor high-voltage power distribution equipment. It seals the load switch, grounding switch and the bus bar of the circuit together in a metal shell, adopts a spring operating mechanism, and uses SF6 gas as an arc extinguishing and insulating medium. It is suitable for ring network power supply or dual radiation power supply of 40.5kV power supply line, which can change the original single radiation power supply mode. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYN61-40.5-armored-mobile-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>KYN61-40.5Z-type armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear hereinafter referred to as switchgear is suitable for three-phase AC 5 0 Hz power systems, used in power plants, substations and industrial and mining enterprises The power distribution room is used to receive and distribute electric energy, and to control, protect and monitor the circuit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GZDW-Intelligent-High-Frequency-DC-Control-Panel</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/pk-series-microcomputer-protection-measurement-and-control-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 15:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/pk-series-microcomputer-protection-measurement-and-control-screen/</guid>
      <description>PK series microcomputer protection measurement and control panels are used in substation distribution substations with voltage levels of 35KV and below. Provide intelligent and networked measurement, protection and control functions for each high-voltage equipment in the station, and at the same time communicate with the upper master station in real time to realize the comprehensive automation of the substation distribution station. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GZDW-Intelligent-High-Frequency-DC-Control-Panel</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/gzdw-intelligent-high-frequency-dc-control-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 14:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/gzdw-intelligent-high-frequency-dc-control-panel/</guid>
      <description>GZDW series DC screen with cadmium nickel battery, floating charger, equipped with automatic detection and alarm device, has long service life, no pollution, convenient maintenance, stable voltage, ultra-low internal resistance output, withstand large current impact and strong adaptability, reliability Advanced features, it is an ideal DC operating power supply device, which can be widely used in substations of 500kV and below and power plants below, and can also be used in metallurgy, mining, petroleum, radio and television, computer rooms, underground railways, high-rise buildings In construction and other departments, it is used as DC control, signal power supply, power failure protection and circuit breaker operating mechanism opening and closing power supply. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XL-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>XL-21 type power cabinet can be widely used in metallurgy, mining, petroleum, chemical industry, electric power, building materials, mechanical processing, transportation, hotels, restaurants It is used for power distribution and open power distribution of three-phase four-wire power system. It provides protection for overload, short circuit and leakage of the line, and performs normal conversion of the circuit.  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/gcs-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 12:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/gcs-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>GCS series combined low-voltage switchgear (hereinafter referred to as GCS complete switchgear). It is suitable for the power system of AC 50~60HZ, rated working voltage AC 380V, rated insulation voltage 660V, 1600KVA and below distribution transformer as power distribution, power, lighting, reactive power compensation, motor control center, and designed in the standard cabinet The mixed system of fixed scheme and withdrawal scheme can meet the different needs of users. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MNS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 11:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>MNS is a modular and multi-functional low-voltage power distribution cabinet, which is used in all low-voltage systems that require high reliability in the fields of metallurgy, petroleum, chemical industry, industrial and mining enterprises, and infrastructure: power distribution box motor control system. The counter structure adopted by MNS has high flexibility. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCK-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>GCK low-voltage switchgear series is called combined low-voltage withdrawable switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear). It is suitable for the power system of AC 50~60HZ, rated working voltage AC 380V, rated insulation voltage 660V, 1600KVA and below distribution transformer as power distribution, power, lighting, reactive power compensation, motor control center, and designed in the standard cabinet The mixed system of fixed scheme and withdrawal scheme can meet the different needs of users. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GGJ-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ggj-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ggj-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>GGJ reactive power compensation device is used in the main circuit and branch circuits of the enterprise power system to improve the power factor and avoid the reactive power from the power system, thereby saving electricity costs. The capacitor automatic switching and cutting set device includes a multi-functional automatic power compensation controller, which has multiple functions such as automatic switching of capacitor banks, measurement and display of various power parameters, and output alarm signals. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATS-dual-power-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ats-dual-power-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ats-dual-power-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>As the name suggests, the ATS dual power distribution box has two power supply lines, which are generally used in low-voltage distribution boxes. The main power supply is generally the city power, which comes from a transformer; the backup power supply is usually supplied from a diesel generator. When working, a controller is used to realize the conversion of the main supply and the backup supply: when the main supply is powered, the controller automatically closes the main supply circuit, that is, the power is supplied by the transformer; when the main supply fails, the controller will give the generator set a The start signal allows the engine to work and supply power. At this time, the backup supply circuit will be charged, and the dual power supply will automatically separate the main supply and close the backup supply. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinets can be widely used in power plants, substations, factories and mines and other power users. In the power distribution system with AC 50Hz, rated working voltage 380 V, and rated current up to 3150 A, it can be used as power, lighting and distribution systems. Electric energy conversion, distribution and control of electrical equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW43-12F-High-Voltage-Intelligent-Vacuum-Circuit-Breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw43-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker-zw43-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw43-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker-zw43-12/</guid>
      <description>ZW43-12 series outdoor high-voltage AC intelligent vacuum circuit breaker (hereinafter referred to as is an outdoor power distribution switchgear with a rated voltage of 12kV and three-phase AC 50Hz. It is mainly composed of the ZW43-12 outdoor high-voltage AC vacuum circuit breaker body , DK series distribution automation feeder terminals, external voltage transformers and control cables, etc., and can be equipped with lightning arresters, single-side isolating switches or double-side isolating switches according to user needs. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-40.5-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-40.5-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-40.5-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32-40.5 outdoor high-voltage vacuum circuit breaker adopts mature box-type sealing structure. It has good sealing performance, so that it is not affected by the external environment, and it is a maintenance-free product. Its spring operating mechanism adopts direct-action chain main drive and multi-stage tripping system, which has high operation reliability and is a good product for pole-mounted circuit breakers. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-24-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-24-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-24-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32-24/630-25 outdoor high-voltage AC vacuum circuit breaker is an outdoor power distribution equipment with a rated voltage of 24kV and three-phase AC 50Hz. It is a switchgear developed by our company according to the long-term planning of my country&amp;#39;s power system and relevant standards. It has the ability to break and close the load current, overload current and short-circuit current in the line. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-12G-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-12g-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:16:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-12g-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32-12(G)/T series outdoor high-voltage AC intelligent vacuum circuit breaker is an outdoor high-voltage power distribution switchgear with a rated voltage of 12kV and three-phase AC 50Hz, mainly used for breaking, It can close the load current, overload current and short-circuit current in the power system. It is suitable for protection and control in the power distribution system of substations and industrial and mining enterprises, and can also be used in places that require frequent operations such as rural power grids. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-12F-High-Voltage-Intelligent-Vacuum-Circuit-Breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 12:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw32-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32F-12F outdoor high-voltage AC intelligent vacuum circuit breaker is a user boundary switch independently developed by our company. It is mainly composed of ZW32-12 type outdoor vacuum circuit breaker body, FDR fault detection controller and external voltage transformer. The three parts are electrically connected through aviation sockets and outdoor sealed control cables. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW20A-12-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20a-12-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 12:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20a-12-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW20A-12 outdoor high-voltage AC vacuum circuit breaker (hereinafter referred to as circuit breaker) is an outdoor power distribution equipment with a rated voltage of 12kV and three-phase AC 50Hz. It uses vacuum arc extinguishing and SF6 gas as the insulating medium, and is an improved product of ZW20-12 column-mounted vacuum circuit breaker. The box body adopts the gas sealing, explosion-proof and insulating structure technology imported from Japan Toshiba Company VSP5, and the sealing performance of the inlet and outlet conduits has also been improved.  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW20-12F-smart-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20-12f-smart-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 11:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20-12f-smart-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW20-12F intelligent vacuum circuit breaker is an advanced product improved from ZW20-12 pole-mounted circuit breaker and FZW28F-12 outdoor boundary vacuum load switch. It has manual and electric operation functions. The switch body adopts Japan Toshiba&amp;#39;s VSP5-12 maintenance-free load switch, and the mature cold-rolled steel box-type sealing structure has good sealing performance, so that it is not affected by the external environment and is a maintenance-free product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FZW28-12F-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/fzw28-12f-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/fzw28-12f-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</guid>
      <description>FZW28(A)-12F outdoor boundary vacuum load switch (VSP5-12 switch body and FDR-01 controller) has fault detection function, protection control function and communication function. It is installed on 10KV overhead line and can realize automatic cutting of single phase Ground faults and phase-to-phase short-circuit faults are automatically isolated. The installation point is suitable for the responsibility demarcation point of the user&amp;#39;s incoming line of 10KV distribution line, and it can also be applied for the branch line connection that meets the requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AB-3S-12-permanent-magnet-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ab-3s-12-permanent-magnet-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ab-3s-12-permanent-magnet-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>AB-3S-12 series outdoor high-voltage vacuum permanent magnet circuit breaker is a new generation of column-mounted vacuum circuit breaker newly developed by integrating advanced technology at home and abroad, adopting new design concepts, and using high-tech means. This product can be used as a switch on the 10kV side of the main transformer of a 35kV substation and a 10kV outgoing line switch, and can also be used as a pole-mounted switch in a distribution network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSP5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/vsp5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/vsp5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</guid>
      <description>VSP5-12 series outdoor vacuum boundary switch is a combination circuit breaker with isolation, rated voltage 12KV, three-phase AC 50HZ high-voltage outdoor switchgear, the built-in voltage 12KV is converted to 220V operating voltage, mainly used for switching on and off rural power grids and urban power grids And load current, overload current, short circuit current of small power system. The overall structure of the product is a three-phase common box type. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-line Soft Start Control Cabinet</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/on-line-soft-start-control-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 10:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/on-line-soft-start-control-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>The online soft starter cabinet uses three-phase parallel thyristors as voltage regulators, which are connected between the power supply and the motor stator. Such a circuit is a three-phase fully controlled bridge rectifier circuit. When using a soft starter to start the motor, the output voltage of the thyristor gradually increases, and the motor gradually accelerates until the thyristor is fully turned on, and the motor works on the mechanical characteristics of the rated voltage to achieve smooth start, reduce the starting current, and avoid starting overcurrent tripping. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Built-in Bypass Soft-Starter</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/built-in-bypass-soft-starter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/built-in-bypass-soft-starter/</guid>
      <description>This series of soft starters adopts a three-input and three-outlet structure design, and the complete set of cabinets does not need an external AC contactor; the interior uses a three-phase independent bypass contactor DC coil design to ensure that it is not affected by voltage drop and thus ensures reliable operation of the equipment! Small and classic, with perfect motor comprehensive protection function! </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three-phase vector inverter</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/vector-inverter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 10:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/vector-inverter/</guid>
      <description>The vector frequency converter is a power control device that uses frequency conversion technology and microelectronics technology to control the AC motor by changing the frequency of the motor&amp;#39;s operating power supply. The frequency converter is mainly composed of rectification, filtering, inverter, braking unit, drive unit, detection unit, micro processing unit etc. The frequency converter adjusts the voltage and frequency of the output power supply by switching off the internal GBT, and provides the required power supply voltage according to the actual needs of the motor, thereby achieving the purpose of energy saving and adjustment. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>External Bypass Soft-Starter</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/external-bypass-soft-starter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/external-bypass-soft-starter/</guid>
      <description>This series of soft starters is an external bypass type, with a structure design of six inputs and three outputs. It is small and exquisite, and has a complete motor comprehensive protection function. The complete set of cabinets does not need an external protector, but it must be used with an external AC contactor. , After the soft starter is started, the AC contactor runs at full pressure, the product is more stable and reliable, and has a long service life.This product is widely used in the starting control of transmission equipment, fans, pumps, crushers and other loads, and the product complies with GB14048.6-2016 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-line soft starter</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/soft-starter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/soft-starter/</guid>
      <description>This series of soft starters adopts three-in, three-out thyristor full-time online structure, and does not need external AC contactors to form a set cabinet; High-power air-cooled radiator and high-speed axial fan are used inside to ensure long-term reliable operation of soft start; When using, be sure to consider the exhaust air in the cabinet to dissipate heat!  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the ten advantages of frequency converters</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/here-are-the-ten-advantages-of-frequency-converters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/here-are-the-ten-advantages-of-frequency-converters/</guid>
      <description>One of the primary advantages of frequency converters is that they can save energy. By adjusting the operating speed of motors to match load requirements, frequency converters can reduce the amount of energy that is wasted during the production process. This not only helps to lower energy costs, but it can also have a positive environmental impact by reducing the amount of greenhouse gas emissions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Invest in a Vector Frequency Inverter for Your Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/why-you-should-invest-in-a-vector-frequency-inverter-for-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/why-you-should-invest-in-a-vector-frequency-inverter-for-your-business/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;#39;s fast-paced and competitive business environment, every penny counts. You need to optimize your operations and minimize your costs in order to remain competitive. One way to do this is to invest in high-quality equipment that can help you save money while improving your overall efficiency. And when it comes to power control, there&amp;#39;s no better solution than a vector frequency inverter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading the Future Trend, Vector Inverter Helps You Easily Control Power Management</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/leading-the-future-trend-vector-inverter-helps-you-easily-control-power-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/leading-the-future-trend-vector-inverter-helps-you-easily-control-power-management/</guid>
      <description>Our vector frequency converter is a game-changing device that provides precision control of your equipment&amp;#39;s speed. It uses advanced technology to precisely regulate the output frequency and voltage of your motors, ensuring that they operate at the optimal level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application of frequency converter in double girder driving</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/application-of-frequency-converter-in-double-girder-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/application-of-frequency-converter-in-double-girder-driving/</guid>
      <description>Driving is a kind of lifting equipment widely used in industrial and mining enterprises. However, the traditional driving control system has high energy consumption, high overall equipment failure rate, high maintenance costs, low power factor of the power grid, and poor speed regulation accuracy, which has been difficult to meet the requirements of modern energy-saving, stable and high-performance equipment. Modern frequency conversion technology is applied to driving equipment, which can realize the main circuit contactless control, small starting current, low noise, accurate walking lifting positioning, high production efficiency, low maintenance cost, and complete frequency converter protection functions, which can effectively protect themselves, motors and other components </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the functions and advantages of the frequency converter?</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/what-are-the-functions-and-advantages-of-the-frequency-converter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/what-are-the-functions-and-advantages-of-the-frequency-converter/</guid>
      <description>Severe vibration will be generated on the motor or the connected mechanical part shaft or gear when it is started by power frequency. This vibration will further increase mechanical wear and loss, reducing the life of mechanical parts and motors. In the frequency conversion speed regulation, the stop method can be controlled, and there are different stop methods to choose </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power up Your Business with Vector Inverters</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/power-up-your-business-with-vector-inverters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/power-up-your-business-with-vector-inverters/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a way to take your business to the next level? Look no further than vector inverters. These powerful devices can help you achieve greater control over your machinery, resulting in increased efficiency, productivity, and profitability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why place an order today for our vector frequency converters</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/why-place-an-order-today-for-our-vector-frequency-converters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/why-place-an-order-today-for-our-vector-frequency-converters/</guid>
      <description>thank you very much for considering purchasing our vector frequency converter. We understand that you need to consider various factors when buying equipment. We hope that through this article, we can introduce some reasons why placing an order for our vector frequency converter today is a wise decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the benefits of using a frequency converter?</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/what-are-the-benefits-of-using-a-frequency-converter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/what-are-the-benefits-of-using-a-frequency-converter/</guid>
      <description>Frequency conversion speed regulation has been recognized as one of the most ideal and promising speed regulation methods. The main purpose of using a general-purpose frequency converter to form a frequency conversion speed regulation transmission system is to meet the needs of improving labor productivity, improving product quality, and improving equipment. The degree of automation, improve the quality of life and improve the living environment and other requirements; the second is to save energy and reduce production costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The company&#39;s English international website officially opened</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/the-companys-english-international-website-officially-opened/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/blog/the-companys-english-international-website-officially-opened/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations on the official opening of the English international website of Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd. The company will provide high-quality products and services to customers around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/about/</guid>
      <description>We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products?
Please feel free to contact us, Our technical staff is available 24/7 for support and fast response, giving full advice on your products and sharing engineering knowledge. Whether you order or not, were always here to support your business.
LINYI SENKUO ELECTROMECHANICAL CO., LTD. E-mail:sales@senkuogroup.com
Mobile/WhatsApp/WeChat:+0086-15064999739
Address:NO. 29, AREA C, FUTUN COMMUNITY, LANSHAN DISTRICT, LINYI CITY, SHANDONG PROVINCE, CHINA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>Frequently asked questions</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
