<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> High voltage circuit breaker on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
    <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/high-voltage-circuit-breaker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  High voltage circuit breaker on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</description>
    <image>
      <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
      <url>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</url>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 12:29:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/high-voltage-circuit-breaker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ZW20A-12-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20a-12-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 12:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20a-12-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW20A-12 outdoor high-voltage AC vacuum circuit breaker (hereinafter referred to as circuit breaker) is an outdoor power distribution equipment with a rated voltage of 12kV and three-phase AC 50Hz. It uses vacuum arc extinguishing and SF6 gas as the insulating medium, and is an improved product of ZW20-12 column-mounted vacuum circuit breaker. The box body adopts the gas sealing, explosion-proof and insulating structure technology imported from Japan Toshiba Company VSP5, and the sealing performance of the inlet and outlet conduits has also been improved.  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW20-12F-smart-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20-12f-smart-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 11:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/zw20-12f-smart-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW20-12F intelligent vacuum circuit breaker is an advanced product improved from ZW20-12 pole-mounted circuit breaker and FZW28F-12 outdoor boundary vacuum load switch. It has manual and electric operation functions. The switch body adopts Japan Toshiba&amp;#39;s VSP5-12 maintenance-free load switch, and the mature cold-rolled steel box-type sealing structure has good sealing performance, so that it is not affected by the external environment and is a maintenance-free product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AB-3S-12-permanent-magnet-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ab-3s-12-permanent-magnet-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ab-3s-12-permanent-magnet-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>AB-3S-12 series outdoor high-voltage vacuum permanent magnet circuit breaker is a new generation of column-mounted vacuum circuit breaker newly developed by integrating advanced technology at home and abroad, adopting new design concepts, and using high-tech means. This product can be used as a switch on the 10kV side of the main transformer of a 35kV substation and a 10kV outgoing line switch, and can also be used as a pole-mounted switch in a distribution network.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
