<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Complete set of switchgear on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd.</title>
    <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/complete-set-of-switchgear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Complete set of switchgear on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd.</description>
    <image>
      <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd.</title>
      <url>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/8.png</url>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/8.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/complete-set-of-switchgear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>XL-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>XL-21 type power cabinet can be widely used in metallurgy, mining, petroleum, chemical industry, electric power, building materials, mechanical processing, transportation, hotels, restaurants It is used for power distribution and open power distribution of three-phase four-wire power system. It provides protection for overload, short circuit and leakage of the line, and performs normal conversion of the circuit.  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MNS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 11:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>MNS is a modular and multi-functional low-voltage power distribution cabinet, which is used in all low-voltage systems that require high reliability in the fields of metallurgy, petroleum, chemical industry, industrial and mining enterprises, and infrastructure: power distribution box motor control system. The counter structure adopted by MNS has high flexibility. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCK-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>GCK low-voltage switchgear series is called combined low-voltage withdrawable switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear). It is suitable for the power system of AC 50~60HZ, rated working voltage AC 380V, rated insulation voltage 660V, 1600KVA and below distribution transformer as power distribution, power, lighting, reactive power compensation, motor control center, and designed in the standard cabinet The mixed system of fixed scheme and withdrawal scheme can meet the different needs of users. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinets can be widely used in power plants, substations, factories and mines and other power users. In the power distribution system with AC 50Hz, rated working voltage 380 V, and rated current up to 3150 A, it can be used as power, lighting and distribution systems. Electric energy conversion, distribution and control of electrical equipment.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
