<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Complete Switch Cabinet on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
    <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/categories/complete-switch-cabinet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Complete Switch Cabinet on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</description>
    <image>
      <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
      <url>https://en.lyskjd.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</url>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 11:50:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://en.lyskjd.com/categories/complete-switch-cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JP-series-integrated-distribution-box-compensation-control-terminal-lighting</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/jp-series-integrated-distribution-box-compensation-control-terminal-lighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 11:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/jp-series-integrated-distribution-box-compensation-control-terminal-lighting/</guid>
      <description>JP series outdoor comprehensive distribution box is designed to meet the requirements of standardization, miniaturization and outdoor type of rural low-voltage power distribution equipment. It integrates power distribution, metering, protection, overload, short circuit, phase loss, undervoltage, Current over-current protection, zero line disconnection protection on the power supply side, automatic reclosing and opening, lightning protection, and capacitor reactive power compensation are integrated, providing a guarantee for safe electricity use in rural areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LKF-transformer-protection-switch-box</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/lkf-transformer-protection-switch-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 10:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/lkf-transformer-protection-switch-box/</guid>
      <description>The transformer protection switch box uses intelligent components to detect the operating current, which can accurately judge the relevant electrical operating conditions. In the event of: overload, short circuit, overvoltage, current imbalance, phase failure, leakage, etc., the smart device can trip within 0.2 seconds according to the above conditions, and automatically reclose the switch about 10 seconds after tripping. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PZ30-modularized-terminal-combined-electric-appliance</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/pz30-modularized-terminal-combined-electric-appliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 10:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/pz30-modularized-terminal-combined-electric-appliance/</guid>
      <description>Pz30 modularized terminal combination electric appliance is a new type of product developed in our country in recent years. It is widely used in industrial and mining enterprises, shops, hospitals, stations, ports, high-rise buildings and residential buildings, etc., as a complete set of equipment for circuit power distribution and control, and protects the circuit from overload, short-circuit leakage, and overvoltage Combined electrical appliances It is used in the end circuit of single-phase three-wire or three-phase five-wire with AC frequency 50Hz, rated voltage 220V or 380V, and maximum total load current of 100A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JXF-series-wall-mounted-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/jxf-series-wall-mounted-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/jxf-series-wall-mounted-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>JXF indoor wall-mounted control box, all products are bent and welded by unbending steel plates, and the surface is electrostatically sprayed with epoxy resin, which is beautiful and durable. The box is equipped with an installation base plate, which can be installed with electrical equipment, and the door can be opened more than 90 degrees and rotated flexibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFW-12-series-cable-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/dfw-12-series-cable-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/dfw-12-series-cable-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>DFW-12 outdoor high-voltage cable distribution box is specially used at the cable node of AC 12kV cable system to distribute electric energy. Its connection method is simple and convenient, and has the characteristics of full insulation, full sealing, corrosion resistance, maintenance-free, and exposed safety parts. It solves the problems of cable T connection and ring network power supply with multiple incoming and outgoing lines with advanced technology. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFW-12-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station-cable-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/dfw-12-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station-cable-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/dfw-12-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station-cable-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>DFW series European-style high-voltage cable branch box is widely used in the node connection of 10KV cable system, and is the main electrical equipment for collecting and branching cables after they come out of the switch cabinet. DFW branch box is designed for outdoor maintenance-free operation, safe and reliable, its protection level is IP33~IP66, and the underground tap can withstand flooding. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LK-DFX-301-10-low-voltage-branch-box</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/lk-dfx-301-10-low-voltage-branch-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/lk-dfx-301-10-low-voltage-branch-box/</guid>
      <description>The branch box is divided into two categories according to its electrical composition: one type does not contain any switchgear, and there are only accessories for processing and connecting cable ends in the box. The structure is relatively simple, the volume is small, and the function is relatively</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stainless-steel-series-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/stainless-steel-series-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/stainless-steel-series-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>The stainless steel series distribution box is a kind of distribution box designed and assembled into various control functions according to the model and specification of the components. Since the size of the box body can be selected arbitrarily, the structure is compact to a quite perfect combination. Wall-mounted installation, it can be used as a see-through window and door, and the door panel is pasted with a sealing rubber strip to prevent rainwater from infiltrating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XJM-metering-box-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/xjm-metering-box-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/xjm-metering-box-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>XJM series metering boxes are suspended or embedded, suitable for the metering of one or more users in civil and commercial residences. The meter box has a multi-door structure, the main switch is installed in the left door, and the watt-hour meter is installed in the right door. , easy to operate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFW-40.5-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/dfw-40.5-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/dfw-40.5-outdoor-opening-and-closing-station/</guid>
      <description>ZGS-12 intelligent integrated substation American box substation is also called prefabricated substation or prefabricated substation. It is a kind of high-voltage switchgear, distribution transformer and low-voltage power distribution device. It is a factory prefabricated indoor and outdoor compact power distribution equipment arranged according to a certain wiring scheme, which is to organically combine functions such as transformer step-down and low-voltage power distribution. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YB33-wind-power-box-type-substation</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/yb33-wind-power-box-type-substation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/yb33-wind-power-box-type-substation/</guid>
      <description>ZGS-12 intelligent integrated substation American box substation is also called prefabricated substation or prefabricated substation. It is a kind of high-voltage switchgear, distribution transformer and low-voltage power distribution device. It is a factory prefabricated indoor and outdoor compact power distribution equipment arranged according to a certain wiring scheme, which is to organically combine functions such as transformer step-down and low-voltage power distribution. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZBW-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-European-style</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zbw-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-european-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zbw-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-european-style/</guid>
      <description>Resin insulated dry-type transformers are our company&amp;#39;s introduction of foreign advanced technology, and independently developed SCB10 and SCB11 series thin-insulated dry-type transformers with fillers. Because the coils are encapsulated by epoxy resin, they are flame retardant, fireproof, explosion-proof, maintenance-free, and pollution-free. , Small size, can be directly installed in the load center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZGS-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-American-style</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zgs-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-american-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zgs-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-american-style/</guid>
      <description>ZGS-12 intelligent integrated substation American box substation is also called prefabricated substation or prefabricated substation. It is a kind of high-voltage switchgear, distribution transformer and low-voltage power distribution device. It is a factory prefabricated indoor and outdoor compact power distribution equipment arranged according to a certain wiring scheme, which is to organically combine functions such as transformer step-down and low-voltage power distribution. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S11-M-10kV-oil-immersed-transformer</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/s11-m-10kv-oil-immersed-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/s11-m-10kv-oil-immersed-transformer/</guid>
      <description>S11-M series fully sealed oil-immersed power transformer has the advantages of low loss, low noise and high efficiency, which can achieve good energy saving effect and reduce pollution. Compared with the ordinary oil-immersed transformer, the fully-sealed transformer cancels the oil storage tank, and the change of oil volume is automatically adjusted and compensated by the elasticity of the corrugated sheet of the corrugated oil tank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S9-M-10kV-three-phase-oil-immersed-fully-sealed-power-transformer</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/s9-m-10kv-three-phase-oil-immersed-fully-sealed-power-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/s9-m-10kv-three-phase-oil-immersed-fully-sealed-power-transformer/</guid>
      <description>S9-M-10kV three-phase oil-immersed fully sealed power transformer is different from ordinary oil-immersed transformers. It cancels the oil storage tank, and the corrugated plate heat sink of the oil tank body is used for heat dissipation and cooling. Its elastic expansion and contraction compensates for the volume of the oil. increase or decrease.  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCB10-10kV-resin-insulated-dry-type-transformer</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/scb10-10kv-resin-insulated-dry-type-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/scb10-10kv-resin-insulated-dry-type-transformer/</guid>
      <description>Resin insulated dry-type transformers are our company&amp;#39;s introduction of foreign advanced technology, and independently developed SCB10 and SCB11 series thin-insulated dry-type transformers with fillers. Because the coils are encapsulated by epoxy resin, they are flame retardant, fireproof, explosion-proof, maintenance-free, and pollution-free. , Small size, can be directly installed in the load center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TBB-10-High-Voltage-Collective-Compensation-Device</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-collective-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-collective-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>The TBB-10 high-voltage collective compensation device mainly avoids the disadvantages of large local compensation investment, equipment maintenance, and decentralized operation management. The centralized compensation device is mainly used in 3-10kV three-phase power frequency AC power system with small load changes. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TBB-10-High-Voltage-Reactive-Power-Automatic-Compensation-Device</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>TBB-10 high-voltage reactive power automatic compensation device is suitable for reactive power automatic tracking compensation of 35kV, 10kV (6kV) buses in 220kV, 110kV, 35kV substations, and is mainly used in 3-35kV three-phase power frequency AC power systems with large load fluctuations , the use of centralized compensation still cannot meet the system requirements, often resulting in over-compensation or under-compensation. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LKGK-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>LCGK-12 fully insulated and fully enclosed inflatable metal switchgear referred to as inflatable cabinet is also known as common box type inflatable cabinet, sf6 inflatable cabinet. All its live parts are completely sealed in a 3.0mm thick stainless steel SF6 gas box, multiple branch switches can be installed in one gas box, so that the switchgear is not affected by the environment. It truly realizes functions such as maintenance-free, reliable operation, and unattended operation. The inflatable cabinet unit adopts a modular design, which can be flexibly expanded and scientifically combined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HXGN17-12-unit-AC-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/hxgn17-12-unit-ac-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/hxgn17-12-unit-ac-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>In the power supply system, it is used to break the load current and close the short-circuit current. The ring network cabinet is equipped with a vacuum load switch, and the replacement mechanism is a spring operating mechanism, which can be operated manually or electrically. The switch and isolating knife are equipped with a dry-action operating mechanism.  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HXGN15-12-box-type-fixed-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:18:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>The principle of ring network power supply: ring network power supply is generally composed of three basic units. The incoming and outgoing line cabinets are used as the ring network unit. When any line fails, it can be isolated in time, and the other unit maintains the continuous power supply of the certified user transformer branch. The user circuit ring network cabinet plays a role of protection and isolation for the transformer, which is convenient for maintenance and repair. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGN68-12-indoor-AC-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/xgn68-12-indoor-ac-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:18:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/xgn68-12-indoor-ac-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>The switchgear is a 3.6, 7.2, 12KV three-phase AC 50Hz single-bus section indoor complete device for receiving and distributing electric energy. It also has the functions of controlling, protecting and monitoring circuits, and can be used in various types of power plants, substations, industrial and mining enterprises, high-rise buildings, etc., and can also be combined with ring main units in switching stations. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYN28-12-armored-removable-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/kyn28-12-armored-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:06:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/kyn28-12-armored-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>KYN28-12 type GZS1armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear) is a three-phase AC 50Hz indoor complete power distribution device, used to receive and non-distribute 3-12KV network power and The circuit implements control protection and supervision. Various types of microcomputer integrated relay protection devices are installed on the panel of the relay chamber of this product, and can realize the intelligent control of the system. It has the functions of remote control, telemetry, remote signaling and remote adjustment, and is controlled by CAN bus with communication interface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGN66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:06:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>XGN66-12Z box-type fixed AC metal-enclosed switchgear referred to as switchgear, this product is suitable for power single busbars with a rated voltage of 3.6-12kv, three-phase AC 50hz, and a rated current of 630A-3150A. Double busbar and single busbar with bypass system are used for receiving and distributing electric energy. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYN28A-24-type-removable-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/kyn28a-24-type-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/kyn28a-24-type-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>This product is suitable for three-phase AC 50/60Hz power system, used to receive and distribute electric energy, and to control, protect and detect the circuit. The switchgear has two structural forms: armored cabinet and double busbar cabinet. It can be equipped with SF6 circuit breaker, VD4-24 circuit breaker, ZN72-24 fully insulated vacuum circuit breaker, and the secondary circuit is equipped with advanced and reliable control protection unit. The interior of the product adopts APG epoxy casting and reliable solid fully insulated busbar technology for full insulation design. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGN15-24-AC-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/xgn15-24-ac-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/xgn15-24-ac-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>XGN15-24 AC high-voltage sulfur hexafluoride ring network switchgear (hereinafter referred to as ring network cabinet) is a new generation of high-voltage electrical products successfully researched by our company by introducing foreign advanced technology and in accordance with the requirements of domestic home appliances and urban network transformation. Strict form test and long-term trial operation assessment, all technical performance indicators have reached the national inspection standards. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HXGN17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/hxgn17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/hxgn17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>HXGN17-40.5 high-voltage vacuum ring network switchgear hereinafter referred to as ring network cabinet is a 50Hz AC three-phase indoor high-voltage power distribution equipment. It seals the load switch, grounding switch and the bus bar of the circuit together in a metal shell, adopts a spring operating mechanism, and uses SF6 gas as an arc extinguishing and insulating medium. It is suitable for ring network power supply or dual radiation power supply of 40.5kV power supply line, which can change the original single radiation power supply mode. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYN61-40.5-armored-mobile-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>KYN61-40.5Z-type armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear hereinafter referred to as switchgear is suitable for three-phase AC 5 0 Hz power systems, used in power plants, substations and industrial and mining enterprises The power distribution room is used to receive and distribute electric energy, and to control, protect and monitor the circuit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GZDW-Intelligent-High-Frequency-DC-Control-Panel</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/pk-series-microcomputer-protection-measurement-and-control-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 15:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/pk-series-microcomputer-protection-measurement-and-control-screen/</guid>
      <description>PK series microcomputer protection measurement and control panels are used in substation distribution substations with voltage levels of 35KV and below. Provide intelligent and networked measurement, protection and control functions for each high-voltage equipment in the station, and at the same time communicate with the upper master station in real time to realize the comprehensive automation of the substation distribution station. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GZDW-Intelligent-High-Frequency-DC-Control-Panel</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/gzdw-intelligent-high-frequency-dc-control-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 14:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/gzdw-intelligent-high-frequency-dc-control-panel/</guid>
      <description>GZDW series DC screen with cadmium nickel battery, floating charger, equipped with automatic detection and alarm device, has long service life, no pollution, convenient maintenance, stable voltage, ultra-low internal resistance output, withstand large current impact and strong adaptability, reliability Advanced features, it is an ideal DC operating power supply device, which can be widely used in substations of 500kV and below and power plants below, and can also be used in metallurgy, mining, petroleum, radio and television, computer rooms, underground railways, high-rise buildings In construction and other departments, it is used as DC control, signal power supply, power failure protection and circuit breaker operating mechanism opening and closing power supply. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XL-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>XL-21 type power cabinet can be widely used in metallurgy, mining, petroleum, chemical industry, electric power, building materials, mechanical processing, transportation, hotels, restaurants It is used for power distribution and open power distribution of three-phase four-wire power system. It provides protection for overload, short circuit and leakage of the line, and performs normal conversion of the circuit.  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/gcs-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 12:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/gcs-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>GCS series combined low-voltage switchgear (hereinafter referred to as GCS complete switchgear). It is suitable for the power system of AC 50~60HZ, rated working voltage AC 380V, rated insulation voltage 660V, 1600KVA and below distribution transformer as power distribution, power, lighting, reactive power compensation, motor control center, and designed in the standard cabinet The mixed system of fixed scheme and withdrawal scheme can meet the different needs of users. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MNS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 11:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>MNS is a modular and multi-functional low-voltage power distribution cabinet, which is used in all low-voltage systems that require high reliability in the fields of metallurgy, petroleum, chemical industry, industrial and mining enterprises, and infrastructure: power distribution box motor control system. The counter structure adopted by MNS has high flexibility. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCK-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>GCK low-voltage switchgear series is called combined low-voltage withdrawable switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear). It is suitable for the power system of AC 50~60HZ, rated working voltage AC 380V, rated insulation voltage 660V, 1600KVA and below distribution transformer as power distribution, power, lighting, reactive power compensation, motor control center, and designed in the standard cabinet The mixed system of fixed scheme and withdrawal scheme can meet the different needs of users. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GGJ-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/ggj-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/ggj-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>GGJ reactive power compensation device is used in the main circuit and branch circuits of the enterprise power system to improve the power factor and avoid the reactive power from the power system, thereby saving electricity costs. The capacitor automatic switching and cutting set device includes a multi-functional automatic power compensation controller, which has multiple functions such as automatic switching of capacitor banks, measurement and display of various power parameters, and output alarm signals. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATS-dual-power-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/ats-dual-power-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/ats-dual-power-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>As the name suggests, the ATS dual power distribution box has two power supply lines, which are generally used in low-voltage distribution boxes. The main power supply is generally the city power, which comes from a transformer; the backup power supply is usually supplied from a diesel generator. When working, a controller is used to realize the conversion of the main supply and the backup supply: when the main supply is powered, the controller automatically closes the main supply circuit, that is, the power is supplied by the transformer; when the main supply fails, the controller will give the generator set a The start signal allows the engine to work and supply power. At this time, the backup supply circuit will be charged, and the dual power supply will automatically separate the main supply and close the backup supply. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinets can be widely used in power plants, substations, factories and mines and other power users. In the power distribution system with AC 50Hz, rated working voltage 380 V, and rated current up to 3150 A, it can be used as power, lighting and distribution systems. Electric energy conversion, distribution and control of electrical equipment.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
