<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Outdoor Switch on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
    <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/tags/outdoor-switch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Outdoor Switch on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</description>
    <image>
      <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
      <url>https://en.lyskjd.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</url>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:29:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://en.lyskjd.com/tags/outdoor-switch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FZW28-12F-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/fzw28-12f-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/fzw28-12f-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</guid>
      <description>FZW28(A)-12F outdoor boundary vacuum load switch (VSP5-12 switch body and FDR-01 controller) has fault detection function, protection control function and communication function. It is installed on 10KV overhead line and can realize automatic cutting of single phase Ground faults and phase-to-phase short-circuit faults are automatically isolated. The installation point is suitable for the responsibility demarcation point of the user&amp;#39;s incoming line of 10KV distribution line, and it can also be applied for the branch line connection that meets the requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSP5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/vsp5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/vsp5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</guid>
      <description>VSP5-12 series outdoor vacuum boundary switch is a combination circuit breaker with isolation, rated voltage 12KV, three-phase AC 50HZ high-voltage outdoor switchgear, the built-in voltage 12KV is converted to 220V operating voltage, mainly used for switching on and off rural power grids and urban power grids And load current, overload current, short circuit current of small power system. The overall structure of the product is a three-phase common box type. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
