<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> High Voltage AC Circuit Breaker on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
    <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/tags/-high-voltage-ac-circuit-breaker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  High Voltage AC Circuit Breaker on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</description>
    <image>
      <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
      <url>https://en.lyskjd.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</url>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:46:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://en.lyskjd.com/tags/-high-voltage-ac-circuit-breaker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ZW43-12F-High-Voltage-Intelligent-Vacuum-Circuit-Breaker</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zw43-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker-zw43-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zw43-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker-zw43-12/</guid>
      <description>ZW43-12 series outdoor high-voltage AC intelligent vacuum circuit breaker (hereinafter referred to as is an outdoor power distribution switchgear with a rated voltage of 12kV and three-phase AC 50Hz. It is mainly composed of the ZW43-12 outdoor high-voltage AC vacuum circuit breaker body , DK series distribution automation feeder terminals, external voltage transformers and control cables, etc., and can be equipped with lightning arresters, single-side isolating switches or double-side isolating switches according to user needs. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-40.5-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zw32-40.5-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zw32-40.5-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32-40.5 outdoor high-voltage vacuum circuit breaker adopts mature box-type sealing structure. It has good sealing performance, so that it is not affected by the external environment, and it is a maintenance-free product. Its spring operating mechanism adopts direct-action chain main drive and multi-stage tripping system, which has high operation reliability and is a good product for pole-mounted circuit breakers. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-24-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zw32-24-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zw32-24-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32-24/630-25 outdoor high-voltage AC vacuum circuit breaker is an outdoor power distribution equipment with a rated voltage of 24kV and three-phase AC 50Hz. It is a switchgear developed by our company according to the long-term planning of my country&amp;#39;s power system and relevant standards. It has the ability to break and close the load current, overload current and short-circuit current in the line. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-12G-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zw32-12g-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:16:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zw32-12g-outdoor-high-voltage-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32-12(G)/T series outdoor high-voltage AC intelligent vacuum circuit breaker is an outdoor high-voltage power distribution switchgear with a rated voltage of 12kV and three-phase AC 50Hz, mainly used for breaking, It can close the load current, overload current and short-circuit current in the power system. It is suitable for protection and control in the power distribution system of substations and industrial and mining enterprises, and can also be used in places that require frequent operations such as rural power grids. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZW32-12F-High-Voltage-Intelligent-Vacuum-Circuit-Breaker</title>
      <link>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zw32-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 12:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://en.lyskjd.com/product/zw32-12f-high-voltage-intelligent-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>ZW32F-12F outdoor high-voltage AC intelligent vacuum circuit breaker is a user boundary switch independently developed by our company. It is mainly composed of ZW32-12 type outdoor vacuum circuit breaker body, FDR fault detection controller and external voltage transformer. The three parts are electrically connected through aviation sockets and outdoor sealed control cables. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
