<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reactive power compensation cabinet on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
    <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/reactive-power-compensation-cabinet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reactive power compensation cabinet on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</description>
    <image>
      <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
      <url>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</url>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/reactive-power-compensation-cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TBB-10-High-Voltage-Reactive-Power-Automatic-Compensation-Device</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>TBB-10 high-voltage reactive power automatic compensation device is suitable for reactive power automatic tracking compensation of 35kV, 10kV (6kV) buses in 220kV, 110kV, 35kV substations, and is mainly used in 3-35kV three-phase power frequency AC power systems with large load fluctuations , the use of centralized compensation still cannot meet the system requirements, often resulting in over-compensation or under-compensation. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GGJ-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ggj-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/ggj-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>GGJ reactive power compensation device is used in the main circuit and branch circuits of the enterprise power system to improve the power factor and avoid the reactive power from the power system, thereby saving electricity costs. The capacitor automatic switching and cutting set device includes a multi-functional automatic power compensation controller, which has multiple functions such as automatic switching of capacitor banks, measurement and display of various power parameters, and output alarm signals. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
