<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>High voltage switchgear on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
    <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/high-voltage-switchgear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in High voltage switchgear on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</description>
    <image>
      <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
      <url>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</url>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/high-voltage-switchgear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TBB-10-High-Voltage-Collective-Compensation-Device</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-collective-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-collective-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>The TBB-10 high-voltage collective compensation device mainly avoids the disadvantages of large local compensation investment, equipment maintenance, and decentralized operation management. The centralized compensation device is mainly used in 3-10kV three-phase power frequency AC power system with small load changes. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TBB-10-High-Voltage-Reactive-Power-Automatic-Compensation-Device</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>TBB-10 high-voltage reactive power automatic compensation device is suitable for reactive power automatic tracking compensation of 35kV, 10kV (6kV) buses in 220kV, 110kV, 35kV substations, and is mainly used in 3-35kV three-phase power frequency AC power systems with large load fluctuations , the use of centralized compensation still cannot meet the system requirements, often resulting in over-compensation or under-compensation. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LKGK-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>LCGK-12 fully insulated and fully enclosed inflatable metal switchgear referred to as inflatable cabinet is also known as common box type inflatable cabinet, sf6 inflatable cabinet. All its live parts are completely sealed in a 3.0mm thick stainless steel SF6 gas box, multiple branch switches can be installed in one gas box, so that the switchgear is not affected by the environment. It truly realizes functions such as maintenance-free, reliable operation, and unattended operation. The inflatable cabinet unit adopts a modular design, which can be flexibly expanded and scientifically combined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HXGN17-12-unit-AC-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn17-12-unit-ac-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn17-12-unit-ac-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>In the power supply system, it is used to break the load current and close the short-circuit current. The ring network cabinet is equipped with a vacuum load switch, and the replacement mechanism is a spring operating mechanism, which can be operated manually or electrically. The switch and isolating knife are equipped with a dry-action operating mechanism.  </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HXGN15-12-box-type-fixed-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:18:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>The principle of ring network power supply: ring network power supply is generally composed of three basic units. The incoming and outgoing line cabinets are used as the ring network unit. When any line fails, it can be isolated in time, and the other unit maintains the continuous power supply of the certified user transformer branch. The user circuit ring network cabinet plays a role of protection and isolation for the transformer, which is convenient for maintenance and repair. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGN68-12-indoor-AC-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn68-12-indoor-ac-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:18:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn68-12-indoor-ac-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>The switchgear is a 3.6, 7.2, 12KV three-phase AC 50Hz single-bus section indoor complete device for receiving and distributing electric energy. It also has the functions of controlling, protecting and monitoring circuits, and can be used in various types of power plants, substations, industrial and mining enterprises, high-rise buildings, etc., and can also be combined with ring main units in switching stations. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYN28-12-armored-removable-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn28-12-armored-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:06:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn28-12-armored-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>KYN28-12 type GZS1armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear) is a three-phase AC 50Hz indoor complete power distribution device, used to receive and non-distribute 3-12KV network power and The circuit implements control protection and supervision. Various types of microcomputer integrated relay protection devices are installed on the panel of the relay chamber of this product, and can realize the intelligent control of the system. It has the functions of remote control, telemetry, remote signaling and remote adjustment, and is controlled by CAN bus with communication interface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGN66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:06:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>XGN66-12Z box-type fixed AC metal-enclosed switchgear referred to as switchgear, this product is suitable for power single busbars with a rated voltage of 3.6-12kv, three-phase AC 50hz, and a rated current of 630A-3150A. Double busbar and single busbar with bypass system are used for receiving and distributing electric energy. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYN28A-24-type-removable-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn28a-24-type-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn28a-24-type-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>This product is suitable for three-phase AC 50/60Hz power system, used to receive and distribute electric energy, and to control, protect and detect the circuit. The switchgear has two structural forms: armored cabinet and double busbar cabinet. It can be equipped with SF6 circuit breaker, VD4-24 circuit breaker, ZN72-24 fully insulated vacuum circuit breaker, and the secondary circuit is equipped with advanced and reliable control protection unit. The interior of the product adopts APG epoxy casting and reliable solid fully insulated busbar technology for full insulation design. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGN15-24-AC-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn15-24-ac-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn15-24-ac-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>XGN15-24 AC high-voltage sulfur hexafluoride ring network switchgear (hereinafter referred to as ring network cabinet) is a new generation of high-voltage electrical products successfully researched by our company by introducing foreign advanced technology and in accordance with the requirements of domestic home appliances and urban network transformation. Strict form test and long-term trial operation assessment, all technical performance indicators have reached the national inspection standards. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HXGN17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>HXGN17-40.5 high-voltage vacuum ring network switchgear hereinafter referred to as ring network cabinet is a 50Hz AC three-phase indoor high-voltage power distribution equipment. It seals the load switch, grounding switch and the bus bar of the circuit together in a metal shell, adopts a spring operating mechanism, and uses SF6 gas as an arc extinguishing and insulating medium. It is suitable for ring network power supply or dual radiation power supply of 40.5kV power supply line, which can change the original single radiation power supply mode. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYN61-40.5-armored-mobile-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>KYN61-40.5Z-type armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear hereinafter referred to as switchgear is suitable for three-phase AC 5 0 Hz power systems, used in power plants, substations and industrial and mining enterprises The power distribution room is used to receive and distribute electric energy, and to control, protect and monitor the circuit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
