<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>High voltage switch cabinet on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
    <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/high-voltage-switch-cabinet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in High voltage switch cabinet on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</description>
    <image>
      <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co. Ltd</title>
      <url>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</url>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/img/mstile-150x150.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:40:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.senkuogroup.com/tags/high-voltage-switch-cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LKGK-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>LCGK-12 fully insulated and fully enclosed inflatable metal switchgear referred to as inflatable cabinet is also known as common box type inflatable cabinet, sf6 inflatable cabinet. All its live parts are completely sealed in a 3.0mm thick stainless steel SF6 gas box, multiple branch switches can be installed in one gas box, so that the switchgear is not affected by the environment. It truly realizes functions such as maintenance-free, reliable operation, and unattended operation. The inflatable cabinet unit adopts a modular design, which can be flexibly expanded and scientifically combined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HXGN15-12-box-type-fixed-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:18:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>The principle of ring network power supply: ring network power supply is generally composed of three basic units. The incoming and outgoing line cabinets are used as the ring network unit. When any line fails, it can be isolated in time, and the other unit maintains the continuous power supply of the certified user transformer branch. The user circuit ring network cabinet plays a role of protection and isolation for the transformer, which is convenient for maintenance and repair. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYN28-12-armored-removable-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn28-12-armored-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:06:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn28-12-armored-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>KYN28-12 type GZS1armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear) is a three-phase AC 50Hz indoor complete power distribution device, used to receive and non-distribute 3-12KV network power and The circuit implements control protection and supervision. Various types of microcomputer integrated relay protection devices are installed on the panel of the relay chamber of this product, and can realize the intelligent control of the system. It has the functions of remote control, telemetry, remote signaling and remote adjustment, and is controlled by CAN bus with communication interface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XGN66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:06:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>XGN66-12Z box-type fixed AC metal-enclosed switchgear referred to as switchgear, this product is suitable for power single busbars with a rated voltage of 3.6-12kv, three-phase AC 50hz, and a rated current of 630A-3150A. Double busbar and single busbar with bypass system are used for receiving and distributing electric energy. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYN61-40.5-armored-mobile-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.senkuogroup.com/product/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>KYN61-40.5Z-type armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear hereinafter referred to as switchgear is suitable for three-phase AC 5 0 Hz power systems, used in power plants, substations and industrial and mining enterprises The power distribution room is used to receive and distribute electric energy, and to control, protect and monitor the circuit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
